<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>my magical myanmar</title><link>http://mymagicalmyanmar.com/</link><description>My Magical Myanmar - Myanmar’s leading Travel Magazine in Hotels, Airlines, Tourism and Travel Trade News</description><language>en-us</language><copyright><![CDATA[  Copyrights © 2017 All Rights Reserved by Logistics Media Services Company Limited. ]]></copyright><image><url>http://mymagicalmyanmar.com/images/logo1.png</url><title>my magical myanmar</title><link>http://mymagicalmyanmar.com/</link></image>
<item>
<title>In Conversation with Photographer  Yu Yu Myint Than</title><link>http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/underground/In Conversation with Photographer  Yu Yu Myint Than</link><pubDate>2018-01-10 05:51:31</pubDate><author>admin</author><category>Underground</category><description>&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img typeof=&quot;foaf:Image&quot; src=&quot;http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/images/posts/642/photos/1515563491-detail1.jpg?itok=vBabesV8&quot; width=&quot;309&quot; height=&quot;166&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yu Yu Myint Than’s latest exhibition, ‘Memory Lane,’ is a collection of dreamy and thought-provoking images inspired by stories of domestic violence and a longing for home. The photos have an abstract quality and beautifully portray personal moments of quiet with subjects deep in thought or exposed on a landscape at dusk. They appear to depict memories or dreams, leaving a lot of interpretation to the viewer. One thing for certain though, is that they are packed with haunting emotion.Yu Yu’s interest in photography came about when she was studying a post-graduate degree in education in Hong Kong.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>The number of foreign visitors to the Shwedagon pagoda dropped by 30,000  </title><link>http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/travelsectorupdates/The number of foreign visitors to the Shwedagon pagoda dropped by 30,000  </link><pubDate>2018-01-10 05:36:55</pubDate><author>admin</author><category>Travel Sector Updates</category><description>&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img typeof=&quot;foaf:Image&quot; src=&quot;http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/images/posts/641/photos/1515562615-detail1.jpg?itok=vBabesV8&quot; width=&quot;309&quot; height=&quot;166&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of foreign  visitors to the Shwedgon Pagoda, the most famous pagoda in Myanmar, dropped by  nearly 30,000 in 2017 compared to the previous year, according to data released  by the Trustee Committee.              There were 615,763 visitors  to the pagoda in 2017 while 2016 saw 646,734 foreign visitors.  It is perhaps due to the  conflict which happened in Rakhine State in August and September and correlates  to the decrease in the number of visitors to Myanmar around the time, according  to the sources in tourism industry.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Exploring Hpa-an  Beyond the Caves</title><link>http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/departures/Exploring Hpa-an  Beyond the Caves</link><pubDate>2018-01-10 05:17:48</pubDate><author>admin</author><category>Departures</category><description>&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img typeof=&quot;foaf:Image&quot; src=&quot;http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/images/posts/640/photos/1515561468-detail1.jpg?itok=vBabesV8&quot; width=&quot;309&quot; height=&quot;166&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s true, in recent years there has been something of a tourism boom in Hpa-an, the capital town of Karen State. This can be attributed to its location along the road between Yangon and the Myaywaddy-Maesot border crossing. It’s also popular with all kinds of Yangonites looking for a breath of fresh air on a long weekend.The landscape of Karen State is majestic. Expansive green flatlands dotted with striking karst mountains and glittering reflections from water-filled rice paddies as far as the eye can see.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
</item>
<item>
<title> Weekend Gateway to  A Forgotten  Hill Town</title><link>http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/departures/ Weekend Gateway to  A Forgotten  Hill Town</link><pubDate>2018-01-10 05:04:52</pubDate><author>admin</author><category>Departures</category><description>&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img typeof=&quot;foaf:Image&quot; src=&quot;http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/images/posts/639/photos/1515560692-detail1.jpg?itok=vBabesV8&quot; width=&quot;309&quot; height=&quot;166&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;HOLIDAYS or vacations are words that bring joy to everyone. As my office was closed four days for Tazaungdaing lighting festival, I decided to go somewhere in a hilly region for holidays.When we think of visiting hilly regions, well-known destinations such as Pyin Oo Lwin, Kalaw, Taunggyi and Lashio are the first ones that come to our mind. Right?But do you know there is a forgotten hilltop town much closer to Yangon? It is named Thandaung Gyi. It was once popular with the British who used it as a summertime retreat during the colonial era.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Travel agencies need to have permit for trips to Naga New Year festival in Nanyun </title><link>http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/travelsectorupdates/Travel agencies need to have permit for trips to Naga New Year festival in Nanyun </link><pubDate>2018-01-10 04:39:56</pubDate><author>admin</author><category>Travel Sector Updates</category><description>&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img typeof=&quot;foaf:Image&quot; src=&quot;http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/images/posts/638/photos/1515559196-detail1.jpg?itok=vBabesV8&quot; width=&quot;309&quot; height=&quot;166&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;Travel  agencies are required to have permit for trips for local and foreign travelers  to Naga ethnic people’s traditional New Year festival to be held in Nanyun,  Sagaing Region, on January 15, according to the recently issued statement by  Myanmar Travel Association.With  the aim to ensure convenience for foreign and local travellers regarding  accommodation and transportation on a Mandalay-Khamti-Lahal-Nanyun trip between  January 12th and 17th and to avoid other unnecessary  matters on the route, organizations and authorities concerned are to work in  cooperation and take responsibility to manage the applications of travel permits  from the Ministry of Hotels and Tourism, said in the statement by the Association  taking reference from a letter from the Ministry which says it aims to enable  the travel agencies to get the permit in time for the festival.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Q & A with Tourism Professionals</title><link>http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/thetalk/Q & A with Tourism Professionals</link><pubDate>2018-01-10 04:22:24</pubDate><author>admin</author><category>The Talk</category><description>&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img typeof=&quot;foaf:Image&quot; src=&quot;http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/images/posts/637/photos/1515558144-detail1.jpg?itok=vBabesV8&quot; width=&quot;309&quot; height=&quot;166&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;Name: Edwin BrielsCountry: originally from the Netherlands,  calling Myanmar home for over 15 yearsJob: Managing Director Khiri Travel Myanmar and volunteer with Myanmar Tourism Marketing in charge of digital marketing and public relationsQuestion: What are your thoughts on the current state of tourism in Myanmar?Answer: I think that tourism in Myanmar has just set off and the sector is ready for growth. The infrastructure has improved a lot and there are plenty of hotel rooms, airline seats, good long distance buses, smooth roads as well as plenty of restaurants, people working in the industry and even excellent mobile internet so the country is ready.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Excellent service and comfortable accommodation in a colonial hotel in Mandalay</title><link>http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/infocus/Excellent service and comfortable accommodation in a colonial hotel in Mandalay</link><pubDate>2018-01-10 03:57:38</pubDate><author>admin</author><category>In Focus</category><description>&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img typeof=&quot;foaf:Image&quot; src=&quot;http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/images/posts/636/photos/1515556658-detail1.jpg?itok=vBabesV8&quot; width=&quot;309&quot; height=&quot;166&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;A couple of months ago I went to Mandalay on a business trip and stayed a night at Hotel Dingar which is located in the downtown area of Mandalay. The special thing about the hotel is that it is located in a colonial building. Mandalay is the second largest city of Myanmar and hotel businesses are facing a lot of competitors nowadays but this hotel stands out because it is not a re-build yet the hotel has brand new look. The other interesting fact is that much of the whole hotel uses teak including in the hotel walls, floors of the bedrooms, furniture and other features.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Experiencing Japanese  Yakiniku  in Mandalay </title><link>http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/infocus/Experiencing Japanese  Yakiniku  in Mandalay </link><pubDate>2018-01-10 03:49:09</pubDate><author>admin</author><category>In Focus</category><description>&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img typeof=&quot;foaf:Image&quot; src=&quot;http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/images/posts/635/photos/1515556149-detail1.jpg?itok=vBabesV8&quot; width=&quot;309&quot; height=&quot;166&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mandalay has a lot of restaurants, street food and traditional foods and though most of these are delicious, I chose Hana Yakiniku for a recent Mandalay meal. Yakiniku means ‘grilled meat’ and customers at this restaurant grill their own meals choosing from a menu offering pork and seafood as well as sushi and other cooked dishes to complete the meal. The restaurant’s special focus is on yakiniku beef with a range of Japanese Kobe and Australian beef.This shop is managed by a Burmese man called Myint Thura Hlaing and he aims to build a Japanese yakiniku culture in Mandalay where it’s rare to find any other Japanese yakiniku restaurants.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Light </title><link>http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/picturesque/Light </link><pubDate>2018-01-09 08:21:54</pubDate><author>admin</author><category>Picturesque</category><description>&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img typeof=&quot;foaf:Image&quot; src=&quot;http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/images/posts/634/photos/1515489714-detail1.jpg?itok=vBabesV8&quot; width=&quot;309&quot; height=&quot;166&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;Third Prize  - Soe Moe Aung&lt;/p&gt;</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Light </title><link>http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/picturesque/Light </link><pubDate>2018-01-09 04:08:58</pubDate><author>admin</author><category>Picturesque</category><description>&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img typeof=&quot;foaf:Image&quot; src=&quot;http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/images/posts/632/photos/1515474538-detail1.jpg?itok=vBabesV8&quot; width=&quot;309&quot; height=&quot;166&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;Second Prize - Nay Lin Aung&lt;/p&gt;</description>
</item></channel></rss>