<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>my magical myanmar</title><link>http://mymagicalmyanmar.com/</link><description>My Magical Myanmar - Myanmar’s leading Travel Magazine in Hotels, Airlines, Tourism and Travel Trade News</description><language>en-us</language><copyright><![CDATA[  Copyrights © 2017 All Rights Reserved by Logistics Media Services Company Limited. ]]></copyright><image><url>http://mymagicalmyanmar.com/images/logo1.png</url><title>my magical myanmar</title><link>http://mymagicalmyanmar.com/</link></image>
<item>
<title>Cable car to be put into service on December 15 at Golden Rock</title><link>http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/travelsectorupdates/Cable car to be put into service on December 15 at Golden Rock</link><pubDate>2017-12-02 18:37:00</pubDate><author>admin</author><category>Travel Sector Updates</category><description>&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img typeof=&quot;foaf:Image&quot; src=&quot;http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/images/posts/578/photos/1512191220-detail1.jpg?itok=vBabesV8&quot; width=&quot;309&quot; height=&quot;166&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;Myanmar’s first ever cable car  service will be ready for visitors at Kyaikhtiyo Pagoda, known as the Golden  Rock, in Mon State, starting from December 15 according to the statement by  Asia Sky, a Korean company carrying out the cable car project in collaboration  with local company Yadana Shwe Sin Construction.     The 1.5 kilometer-long cable car  project is being implemented on a 13.5-acre area of land with the aim to enable  visitors to travel more easily to the pagoda located on the top of a  3,609-foot mountain.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hotel Boss</title><link>http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/arrivals/Hotel Boss</link><pubDate>2017-11-30 21:36:23</pubDate><author>admin</author><category>Arrivals</category><description>&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img typeof=&quot;foaf:Image&quot; src=&quot;http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/images/posts/559/photos/1512454322-detail1.jpg?itok=vBabesV8&quot; width=&quot;309&quot; height=&quot;166&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warmly Welcome From Mandalay Hotel Boss Location (Our Hotel location nearly the heart of Zay Cho  Market and Ayarwaddy  River is down town area near by Eain Daw Yar Pagoda.)Restaurant (Guest can enjoy the variety of Asian and International cuisine. At the Sky Bar beauty of sunrise and sunset view in restaurantOur Guest Rooms are typical luxurious furniture and deep cleaning and so smart.For reservation: 02 60067, 02 64342&lt;/p&gt;</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hana Yakiniku Japanese BBQ Restaurant </title><link>http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/arrivals/Hana Yakiniku Japanese BBQ Restaurant </link><pubDate>2017-11-30 21:27:57</pubDate><author>admin</author><category>Arrivals</category><description>&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img typeof=&quot;foaf:Image&quot; src=&quot;http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/images/posts/557/photos/1512028677-detail1.jpg?itok=vBabesV8&quot; width=&quot;309&quot; height=&quot;166&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;HANA YAKINIKU Japanese BBQ Restaurant is the first in Mandalay to offer Kobe Wine Beef from Japan. Customers can enjoy the full Yakiniku, (Japanese Grill), style dinning experience in a smoke-free environment.Address: No. A1, 27th Street, Between of 68th &amp; 69th Street, Chan Aye Thar Zan Township, Mandalay.Tel: 09 978442988, 09 962577160Email: info@hanayakiniku.comFacebook: www.facebook.com/HanaMDL1Instagram: &lt;/p&gt;</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Down Time in Mandalay City</title><link>http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/underground/Down Time in Mandalay City</link><pubDate>2017-11-30 21:18:53</pubDate><author>admin</author><category>Underground</category><description>&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img typeof=&quot;foaf:Image&quot; src=&quot;http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/images/posts/555/photos/1512028133-detail1.jpg?itok=vBabesV8&quot; width=&quot;309&quot; height=&quot;166&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;BY LWIN MAR HTUNInternational travellers and local visitors alike want to enjoy the night life of Mandalay while visiting the city and so do I, but on a recent trip to scope out the scene, I found it to be totally unlike Yangon. Mandalay has more beer stations and fewer bars. Most of the bars are closed early at night (around 11pm) so night life seems to have very limited options. At the same time I decided to check out the spa and relaxation options around the city and was impressed by how many spas there are in Mandalay.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Making Food is Like Making Art</title><link>http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/standout/Making Food is Like Making Art</link><pubDate>2017-11-30 20:56:52</pubDate><author>admin</author><category>Standout</category><description>&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img typeof=&quot;foaf:Image&quot; src=&quot;http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/images/posts/554/photos/1512026812-detail1.jpg?itok=vBabesV8&quot; width=&quot;309&quot; height=&quot;166&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Lwin Mar HtunJaggery, which is a brown-colored block harvested from toddy palm juice, is a traditional dessert served after lunch and dinner to help digestion. Nowadays, some local restaurants still offer jaggery after a meal but most people have forgotten the traditional sweet. One day, a girl happened to try eat her jaggery as a dessert after her meal and she couldn’t finish the whole block. The ‘Tree Food’ Myanmar traditional jaggery brand idea started from that day.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Yangon Untravelled - 6</title><link>http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/departures/Yangon Untravelled - 6</link><pubDate>2017-11-30 20:49:01</pubDate><author>admin</author><category>Departures</category><description>&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img typeof=&quot;foaf:Image&quot; src=&quot;http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/images/posts/553/photos/1512026341-detail1.jpg?itok=vBabesV8&quot; width=&quot;309&quot; height=&quot;166&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Rangoon War Cemetery (Kyun Taw Road, San Chaung Township)On the topic of graves, the Rangoon War Cemetery (lesser-known that the Taukkyan War Cemetery north of the city) contains the graves or memorials honouring the memory of 1,381 soldiers who died in the Second World War and 56 soldiers who died in Rangoon during the First World War. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Yangon Untravelled - 5</title><link>http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/departures/Yangon Untravelled - 5</link><pubDate>2017-11-30 20:39:53</pubDate><author>admin</author><category>Departures</category><description>&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img typeof=&quot;foaf:Image&quot; src=&quot;http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/images/posts/552/photos/1512025793-detail1.jpg?itok=vBabesV8&quot; width=&quot;309&quot; height=&quot;166&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;St Mary’s Cathedral  (Corner of Bogyoke Road and Bo Aung Kyaw Street, Kyauktada Township)  The Shwedagon Pagoda is the sightseeing king of Yangon, but the Catholics made a good faith effort with St Mary’s Cathedral, a vast edifice of towers and spires completed in 1911 by Dutch architect Father Hendrick Janzen who started with “only bricks and cement” according to the Yangon archdiocese website. The Anglican Holy Trinity Cathedral on the other end of Bogyoke Road (near Bogyoke Market) is somewhat more plain (in Protestant fashion), but for some reason they keep rabbits, guinea pigs, turkeys and monkeys on the grounds as pets.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Yangon Untravelled - 4</title><link>http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/departures/Yangon Untravelled - 4</link><pubDate>2017-11-30 20:32:01</pubDate><author>admin</author><category>Departures</category><description>&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img typeof=&quot;foaf:Image&quot; src=&quot;http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/images/posts/551/photos/1512025321-detail1.jpg?itok=vBabesV8&quot; width=&quot;309&quot; height=&quot;166&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Tomb of Bahadur Shah Zafar (Zi Wa Ka Street, just south of Shwedagon Pagoda)The last emperor of India, Bahadur Shah Zafar, rests in Yangon—a fact taken for granted by Muslim visitors from India, but lesser-known to ordinary tourists.Bahadur Shah Zafar died in 1862 after he was exiled to British Burma following a failed rebellion. But the original site of his burial was forgotten (or concealed) until 1991, when some ditch-diggers uncovered the tomb of the “Emperor-Saint.” The tomb, the original symbolic tomb and the tombs of Bahadur Shah Zafar’s wife and granddaughter are available for viewing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Introducing the Dokhtawady River</title><link>http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/departures/Introducing the Dokhtawady River</link><pubDate>2017-11-30 20:16:39</pubDate><author>admin</author><category>Departures</category><description>&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img typeof=&quot;foaf:Image&quot; src=&quot;http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/images/posts/549/photos/1512122490-detail1.jpg?itok=vBabesV8&quot; width=&quot;309&quot; height=&quot;166&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gliding along the Dokhtawady River, we pass blissful, bathing water buffalo, only their heads and twitching ears visible above the water. We chug past sprawling banyan trees, their exposed roots creeping along the muddy richness of the river bank soil, their lofty branches offering brief respites of shade. Shan locals are all around using the river for bathing or transporting their precious harvests. Acres and acres of towering sweet corn crops wave to us as we make our way along the coffee-coloured river through northern Shan State and moving east of Hsipaw.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Trekking (3)</title><link>http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/picturesque/Trekking (3)</link><pubDate>2017-11-30 19:49:20</pubDate><author>admin</author><category>Picturesque</category><description>&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;img typeof=&quot;foaf:Image&quot; src=&quot;http://www.mymagicalmyanmar.com/images/posts/548/photos/1512022760-detail1.jpg?itok=vBabesV8&quot; width=&quot;309&quot; height=&quot;166&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;Third Prize - Kaung Zaw Hein (GaYat) &lt;/p&gt;</description>
</item></channel></rss>